{
    "subject": "resource/2009_in_Brazilian_football",
    "predicate": "property/l",
    "object": "11",
    "human_readable": "The level of Brazilian football in 2009 was 11.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9256702661514282,
            "question": "What was the level of Brazilian football in 2009?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7114025354385376,
            "question": "What factors might have contributed to the high level of Brazilian football in 2009?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6150251626968384,
            "question": "On a scale of 1-10, how would you rate the performance of Brazilian football in 2009?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5871036052703857,
            "question": "How did the level of Brazilian football in 2009 impact global perceptions of the sport?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5689795613288879,
            "question": "How did the performance of Brazilian football in 2009 compare to previous years?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3135828971862793,
            "question": "What were some key developments or trends in Brazilian football during this year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2910548746585846,
            "question": "Were there any significant tournaments or events held in Brazil during 2009?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2883065938949585,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of notable players from Brazil in 2009?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2545251250267029,
            "question": "What were some of the challenges facing Brazilian football during this period?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1827511340379715,
            "question": "Did any international teams pose a threat to Brazilian dominance in 2009?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The level of Brazilian football in 2009 was 11.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3270_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some of the challenges facing Brazilian football during this period?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3270_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide examples of notable players from Brazil in 2009?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3270_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any significant tournaments or events held in Brazil during 2009?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3270_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3270_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3270_135.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3270_146.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3270_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3270_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3270_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3270_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3270_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3270_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3270_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'} \n``` \n\n\nThe text provided does not mention a specific numerical level assigned to Brazilian football in 2009.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not contain any information about the level of Brazilian football in 2009 or any other year, nor does it mention a specific numerical level for the league. Therefore, the statement \"The level of Brazilian football in 2009 was 11\" cannot be supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}